{
    "id": "6c3e3715073d424c83190671b1c9d8a5",
    "title": "Prepositions of movement: grammar exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "d0237bad35994db1a71bc71e1a11c7ec",
            "title": "Prepositions Of Movement",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I don’t know how I managed to get ………………… this mess.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "into",
                        "on to",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I hope you won’t run …………………. any problems.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "on to",
                        "into"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He was trying to throw his hat ……………….. the roof.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "into",
                        "on to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "John always manages to get ……………… trouble.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "on to",
                        "into"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He threw himself …………………. the work with great enthusiasm.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "into",
                        "on to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ran ………………….. the room.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "out of",
                        "of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I took the envelope …………………. my pocket.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "out from",
                        "out of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She sat there staring ………………….. the window.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "on to",
                        "on",
                        "out of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "John wants to get ………………… advertising.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "in",
                        "into"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He promised that he would look ………………….. the matter.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "on to",
                        "into"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}